Exercise 5-5, R Combinations. Don't think about spelling here, just pronounce each
column of words as the heading indicates.
dirt, stir, sir, burn, art, heart, hard, part, far, farm, cathartic, mar, spar,
sharp, char, guard, car, tar, dark, star, sorry, barn, air, hair, haired, pair,
wear, aware, wear, fair, fairy, there, mare, spare, share, chair, scared, care,
tear, dare, stare, Sarah, bear, ore, horse, hoard, pour, war, award, warm, for,
form, thawr, more, sport, shore, chore, gourd, core, tour, door, store, sore,
born. ear,
hear, hears, peer, wear, a weird, weird, fear, fierce, theory, mere, spear, sheer,
cheer geared Kier tear dear steer seer beer hour hour power flower 11th hour
shower chowder gower cower tower dower sour bower